<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>@randelltuazon Blog</title>
        <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets</link>
        <description>@randelltuazon Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elusive One]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/elusive-one</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/elusive-one</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When in God's time I with you be introduced,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When in God's time I with you be introduced,<br>
I'll urge perfection for such a perfect muse.<br>
I'd cherry-pick the sweetest words, by fair chance<br>
Align our first talk in sweet deliverance.<br>
Yet I fear to try too much and please you none,<br>
And be lost forever, my elusive one.<br>
Or in regret be drowned of what might have been<br>
That I spent the idle night, much into thinking.<br>
And unto my excitements, my senses wake,<br>
Out of overmuch preparations to make<br>
Than be well-rested, had gotten weary instead<br>
Rehearsing sweet thoughts bubbling over my head.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> But doubt this may and never bound to happen,<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> That I tire depend wishing things to Heaven.</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bittersweet Dream]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/bittersweet-dream</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/bittersweet-dream</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Let not my dream comprise you and be it sweet]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Let not my dream comprise you and be it sweet<br>
When my desire hungers more throughout of sleep<br>
Whilst stars write plots of perfect Love above all<br>
By when you take and play my lovely wife's role.<br>
A fool deceived, to be convinced 'tis heaven<br>
Blinding me of a prize, fate has forbidden:<br>
The warmth felt in your hand, softer as it grips<br>
The sunrise in your smile, and delicate lips.<br>
Such fragile qualities, I refuse to touch.<br>
Gratified by these though I covet so much.<br>
'Till truth itself reveals, and the curtains close,<br>
Bleed you my first thought when reality rose.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> If I dream another, and still find you there<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> Then let it be my last, hence dream forever.<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What's Not to Love?]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/whats-not-to-love</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/whats-not-to-love</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[If your concerns suspect of why I'm in love,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If your concerns suspect of why I'm in love,<br>
Cast do the doubts away, for what's not to love?<br>
By voice of one remark reveals another,<br>
In no resolve with time begets more wonder.<br>
Of all your beauty, I confuse what's foremost<br>
No compliment could suffice your doubts almost.<br>
'Cause all I know, you are so much lovable;<br>
Far beyond my league and insurmountable.<br>
But I do not love you because of reason,<br>
Nor what attends presently at my vision,<br>
For my heart does not think, nor does mind to see<br>
I'll love you still, be certain or mystery.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> But if you still protest, I would not say more,<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> Let me just confirm my love for keeps therefore.<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Purely]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/purely</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/purely</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[I love you without lust, nor doubts, nor demise,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I love you without lust, nor doubts, nor demise,<br>
When a kiss in the cheek would even suffice.<br>
Each shared nights I care only to watch you sleep,<br>
Softly brushing your hair through my fingertips.<br>
I pray to be the right one such grace deserves,<br>
My appeal is not your beauty nor your curves.<br>
I have a thousand fantasies, but none of you,<br>
I'd rather dream about us and smile afew.<br>
I'd carry all burdens when the worst demands,<br>
And in our fifties, we'd still be holding hands.<br>
For my love is timeless, beyond heart and soul,<br>
I'll love you even without hope, nor you at all.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> Even if it may not always seem to show,<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> I love you purely more than you ever know.<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Missing You Already]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/missing-you-already</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/missing-you-already</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[I love you in the most unselfish possible way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I love you in the most unselfish possible way.<br>
Secretly, subtle, gentle and tame.<br>
I love you in a way I am so much willing to suffer,<br>
With a heart constantly breaking, day after day after day.<br>
I love you beyond words, before myself and above all,<br>
Every little now and then.<br>
By sweet thoughts of you, there's a pinch in the heart,<br>
Of the certain downfall, that my heart so neverminds.<br>
I'll love you still even when you don't<br>
And even if I get lost, you will always be home.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->  Soon, all of this will be a bittersweet memory,<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->  You're still here, but I'm missing you already<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mute Was I of Sweet Lines]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/mute-was-i-of-sweet-lines</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/mute-was-i-of-sweet-lines</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[None more so to say, swayed I in an instant]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>None more so to say, swayed I in an instant<br>
My day rises at presence of your radiance.<br>
I beseech heaven draw forth all these jitters,<br>
That then I find myself lost in deeper prayers.<br>
For yours is a beauty resembling a goddess,<br>
Sustained upon perfectly at all angles.<br>
My eyes troubled into looking straight with yours,<br>
For I'll be melting, and more my heart implores<br>
All the beauty safe contained in those graces,<br>
But mute was I of any sweet lines and phrases.<br>
Knownst you barely, doubt me if it's all true,<br>
It is but madness, I cannot say I love you.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> And torn with regrets, what ifs and whatnot,<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> Would I've been any better to have earned your heart?<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Your Loveliness]]></title>
            <link>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/your-loveliness</link>
            <guid>https://ekupaskibas18.github.io/blogs/sonnets/your-loveliness</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Lovely is the morning, you are lovelier...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lovely is the morning, you are lovelier...<br>
Like an angel divine has fallen here,<br>
Spare me, what a vision oh my lucky charm<br>
While I strive hard to look more seemingly calm.<br>
Please, last the fading day, and althrough the night.<br>
Remain from me alive, You by borrowed sight.<br>
For uncertain tomorrows may be unblessed,<br>
And lest I may ran out of your loveliness.<br>
Through weekends' boredom I myself come weary,<br>
A day none of you is only misery.<br>
Most treasured You, never had but neither lost.<br>
Beknown this lifetime we'll never come across.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> Shall fate robs this, I can no longer accept.<br>
<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- -->&nbsp;<!-- --> For it's all I have of you and ever kept.<br></p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>poetry</category>
            <category>sonnet</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>